[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The muscular system composes what percent of total body weight?", "correct_answer": "35% - 50%", "incorrect_answers": ["25% - 35%", "10% - 15%", "60% - 70%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island is one of Indonesias 33 provinces.", "correct_answer": "Bali", "incorrect_answers": ["Java", "Sumatra", "Lombok"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you add a ladle of broth to the risotto, it should be in this condition.", "correct_answer": "Simmering", "incorrect_answers": ["Unsalted", "Cold", "Sweetened"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Warner Bros. cartoon character uses the name of the Native American meal succotash as a catchphrase?", "correct_answer": "Sylvester", "incorrect_answers": ["Bugs Bunny", "Daffy Duck", "Tweety"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1955 comedy movie features the iconic scene with Marilyn Monroes white dress lifted by the air draft?", "correct_answer": "The Seven Year Itch", "incorrect_answers": ["Were Not Married!", "All About Eve", "The Prince and the Showgirl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This speciality comes straight from the outbacks of Australia.  It is the white larvae of the ghost moth that are often found in trunks and roots of trees.", "correct_answer": "Witchetty grubs", "incorrect_answers": ["Geoduck clams", "Sashimi", "Baalut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy duo started as a nightclub act in the late 1940s and made several successful movies in the 1950s before breaking up for good in 1956.", "correct_answer": "Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["John Jacobs and Frank Sinatra", "Frank Sinatra and Dean Martin", "Dan Rowan and Dick Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Elizabeth Taylors second husband?", "correct_answer": "Michael Wilding", "incorrect_answers": ["Mike Todd", "Nick Hilton", "Eddie Fisher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these movies did not win 10 Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Amadeus", "incorrect_answers": ["Titanic", "Ben-Hur", "The Lord of the Rings: The return of the King"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Tony Maneros brother, portrayed by actor Martin Shakar in the movie Saturday Night Fever?", "correct_answer": "Frank", "incorrect_answers": ["Joey", "Domenick", "Johnny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A plane travels at 176 miles per hour for 4 hours from Chicago due East. What is the planes velocity?", "correct_answer": "176 mph East", "incorrect_answers": ["176 mph", "44 mph East", "5.5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Located at the Peterson Air Force base in Colorado, NORAD is a military organization that tracks aircraft, missiles and space vehicles. It also tracks what fictional character?", "correct_answer": "Santa", "incorrect_answers": ["The Easter Bunny", "The Tooth Fairy", "None of these"]}]